Guide to the Arlen Specter Senatorial Papers, Group 4. Office Administration Files, 1962-2010 TJU.2010.01.04
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Administrative Assistant Files, 1962-2010; I.
  - Gil Stein, 1966-2000; 33.
    - Weapons of mass destruction (WMD), 1999 (Box 652, Folder 14)
    - WMD, CRS Nuclear Proliferation Factbook, 1994 (Box 652, Folder 15)
    - WMD, Current and projected national security threats hearing, 1996 (Box 652, Folder 16)
    - WMD, Department of Energy briefing, 1998 (Box 652, Folder 17)
    - WMD, Documentation of presentations to the Commission, 1998 (Box 652, Folder 18)
    - WMD, Final report, undated (Box 652, Folder 19)
    - WMD, Global proliferation of WMD hearing, 1996 (Box 652, Folder 20-21)
    - WMD, Materials, April 2-9, 1998 (Box 652, Folder 22)
    - WMD, Materials, April 3, 1998 (Box 652, Folder 23)
    - WMD, Materials, April 7, 1998 (Box 652, Folder 24)
    - WMD, Materials, April 28, 1998 (Box 652, Folder 25)
    - WMD, Materials, May 21, 1998 (Box 652, Folder 26)
    - WMD, Materials, January 28-29, 1999 (Box 652, Folder 27)
    - WMD, Materials, February 11, 1999 (Box 653, Folder 1)
    - WMD, Materials, February 25, 1999 (Box 653, Folder 2)
    - WMD, Materials, May 1999 (Box 653, Folder 3)
    - WMD, Members and materials, 1998 (Box 653, Folder 4)
    - WMD, Outside experts, 1998 (Box 653, Folder 5)
    - WMD, Proliferation news, 1999 (Box 653, Folder 6)
    - WMD, Proliferation threats of the 1990s hearing, 1993 (Box 653, Folder 7)
    - WMD, Report draft, June 14, 1999 (Box 653, Folder 8)
    - WMD, Report draft, June 23, 1999 (Box 653, Folder 9)
    - WMD, Select Committee on Intelligence reports, 1996 (Box 653, Folder 10)
    - WMD, Worldwide Intelligence Review hearing, 1995 (Box 653, Folder 11)
    - Youth violence, Christianity Today, 1998-1999 (Box 653, Folder 12)
  - Mary Styn, 2000-2010; 34.
    Mary Styn served as: staff assistant, 2005-2008; and executive director, Erie office, 2009-2010.
    - Trip files, 2000-2001 (Box 653, Folder 13)
    - Trip files, 2002 (Box 653, Folder 14)
    - Trip files, 2003 (Box 653, Folder 15)
    - Trip files, January-April 2004 (Box 653, Folder 16)
    - Trip files, August-September 2004 (Box 653, Folder 17)
    - Trip files, 2006 (Box 653, Folder 18)
    - Trip files, 2007 (Box 653, Folder 19)
    - Trip files, 2008 (Box 653, Folder 20)
    - Trip files, 2009 (Box 653, Folder 21)
  - Lonnie Taylor, 1981-1987; 35.
    Lonnie Taylor served as: staff assistant, 1981-1984; office manager and executive director, 1985-1986; and appropriations and budget staff, 1987.
    - Constituent Mail System (CMS) form letters, 1980s (Box 653, Folder 22)
    - Treasury and postal accomplishments, 1980s (Box 653, Folder 23)
    - Campaign Committee, 1981 (Box 653, Folder 24)
    - Chronological file, 1981 (Box 653, Folder 25)
    - CMS, Disagreement letters, 1981 (Box 653, Folder 26-27)
    - CMS, Mail reports, 1981 (Box 653, Folder 28)
    - CMS, Mail reports, 1981 (Box 654, Folder 1-2)
    - CMS, Permanent files, 1981 (Box 654, Folder 3-4)
    - CMS, Regional office mail reports, 1981 (Box 654, Folder 5)
    - CMS, Weekly item stat reports, 1981 (Box 654, Folder 6-7)
    - Master plan, 1981 (Box 654, Folder 8)
    - Office procedures, 1981 (Box 654, Folder 9-10)
    - Voting/elections, 1981-1982 (Box 654, Folder 11)
    - Annual objectives, 1982 (Box 654, Folder 12)
    - Budget, 1982 (Box 654, Folder 13)
    - Chronological file, 1982 (Box 654, Folder 14)
    - CMS, Annual report, 1982 (Box 654, Folder 15)
    - CMS, Mail reports, 1982 (Box 654, Folder 16)
    - CMS, Permanent files, 1982 (Box 654, Folder 17)
    - CMS, Regional mail office reports, 1982 (Box 654, Folder 18)
    - CMS, Weekly item stat reports, 1982 (Box 654, Folder 19-20)
    - CMS, Weekly profession code counts, 1982 (Box 655, Folder 1)
    - Bill Loughrey, 1982 (Box 655, Folder 2-5)
    - Memos, Specter to staff, 1982 (Box 655, Folder 6)
    - Memos, Taylor to Specter, 1982 (Box 655, Folder 7)
    - Memos, Taylor to staff, 1982 (Box 655, Folder 8)
    - Miscellaneous, 1982 (Box 655, Folder 9)
    - CMS, Mail status reports, 1981-1983 (Box 655, Folder 10)
    - Allentown office, 1983 (Box 655, Folder 11)
    - Chronological file, 1983 (Box 655, Folder 12)
    - CMS, 1983 (Box 655, Folder 13)
    - CMS, Mail reports, January-March 1983 (Box 655, Folder 14)
    - CMS, Mail reports, April-June 1983 (Box 655, Folder 15)
    - CMS, Mail reports, July-September 1983 (Box 655, Folder 16-17)
    - CMS, Mail reports, October-December 1983 (Box 655, Folder 18)
    - CMS, New and updated items, 1983 (Box 655, Folder 19)
    - CMS, Regional office mail reports, 1983 (Box 655, Folder 20)
    - Ethics Committee inquiries, 1983 (Box 655, Folder 21)
    - Mail, 1983 (Box 655, Folder 22)
    - Memos, Specter to staff, 1983 (Box 655, Folder 23)
    - Memos, Taylor to Specter, 1983 (Box 655, Folder 24)
    - Memos, Taylor to staff, 1983 (Box 656, Folder 1)
    - Minority affairs, 1983 (Box 656, Folder 2)
    - Miscellaneous, 1983 (Box 656, Folder 3)
    - Open houses, 1983 (Box 656, Folder 4)
    - Point Pleasant, 1983 (Box 656, Folder 5)
    - Press mail, 1983 (Box 656, Folder 6)
    - Travel, 1983 (Box 656, Folder 7)
    - Appropriations, 1984 (Box 656, Folder 8-10)
    - Archives, 1984 (Box 656, Folder 11)
    - Budget, 1984 (Box 656, Folder 12-16)
    - Buffalo District Army Corps of Engineers, 1984 (Box 656, Folder 17)
    - Casework reports, 1984 (Box 656, Folder 18)
    - Chronological file, January-March 1984 (Box 656, Folder 19)
    - Chronological file, April-June 1984 (Box 657, Folder 1)
    - Chronological file, July-September 1984 (Box 657, Folder 2)
    - Chronological file, October-December 1984 (Box 657, Folder 3)
    - CMS, Abstract reports, 1984 (Box 657, Folder 4)
    - CMS, Mail reports, January-March 1984 (Box 657, Folder 5-6)
    - CMS, Mail reports, April-December 1984 (Box 657, Folder 7)
    - CMS, Output reports, 1984 (Box 657, Folder 8)
    - CMS, Regional office mail reports, 1984 (Box 657, Folder 9)
    - CMS, Weekly item stat reports, 1984 (Box 657, Folder 10)
    - CMS, Weekly profession code counts, 1984 (Box 657, Folder 11)
    - CMS, Zip and area code stats, 1984 (Box 657, Folder 12)
    - Economic development, 1984 (Box 657, Folder 13)
    - Election results, 1984 (Box 657, Folder 14)
    - Ethics Committee inquiries, 1984 (Box 657, Folder 15)
    - International Monetary Fund, 1984 (Box 657, Folder 16)
    - Joint casework, 1984 (Box 657, Folder 17)
    - Memos, General, 1984 (Box 657, Folder 18)
    - Memos, Specter to staff, 1984 (Box 657, Folder 19)
    - Memos, Taylor to Specter, 1984 (Box 657, Folder 20-21)
    - Memos, Taylor to Specter, 1984 (Box 658, Folder 1)
    - Memos, Taylor to staff, 1984 (Box 658, Folder 2)
    - Miscellaneous, 1984 (Box 658, Folder 3)
    - North East Township harbor, 1984 (Box 658, Folder 4)
    - Pennypack Creek, 1984 (Box 658, Folder 5)
    - Presque Isle, 1984 (Box 658, Folder 6)
    - Schuylkill River, 1984 (Box 658, Folder 7)
    - Seascape, 1984 (Box 658, Folder 8)
    - Special mailings, 1984 (Box 658, Folder 9)
    - Water bill, 1984 (Box 658, Folder 10)
    - West Little Pine Creek, 1984 (Box 658, Folder 11)
    - York wastewater plant, 1984 (Box 658, Folder 12)
    - Appropriations, 1985 (Box 658, Folder 13)
    - Budget, 1985 (Box 658, Folder 14-15)
    - Campaign, 1985 (Box 658, Folder 16)
    - Casework reports, 1985 (Box 658, Folder 17)
    - China nuclear trade agreement, 1985 (Box 658, Folder 18)
    - Congressional Records, 1985 (Box 658, Folder 19)
    - CMS, Abstract reports, 1985 (Box 658, Folder 20)
    - CMS, Mail reports, 1985 (Box 658, Folder 21)
    - CMS, Mass mailings, 1985 (Box 658, Folder 22)
    - CMS, Output reports, 1985 (Box 658, Folder 23)
    - CMS, Regional office mail reports, 1985 (Box 658, Folder 24)
    - CMS, Zip and area code stats, 1985 (Box 658, Folder 25)
    - Continuing resolution, 1985 (Box 658, Folder 26)
    - Daily newsclips, 1985 (Box 659, Folder 1)
    - Delaware River Basin, 1985 (Box 659, Folder 2)
    - Floods, 1985 (Box 659, Folder 3)
    - Inauguration, 1985 (Box 659, Folder 4)
    - Japan teleconference, 1985 (Box 659, Folder 5)
    - Letters not sent, 1985 (Box 659, Folder 6)
    - Memos, General, 1985 (Box 659, Folder 7-9)
    - Memos, Specter to staff, 1985 (Box 659, Folder 10)
    - Memos, Staff to Specter, 1985 (Box 659, Folder 11-12)
    - Memos, Taylor to Specter, 1985 (Box 659, Folder 13)
    - Minority affairs, 1985 (Box 659, Folder 14)
    - Miscellaneous, 1985 (Box 659, Folder 15)
    - Miscellaneous bills, 1985 (Box 659, Folder 16)
    - Open houses, 1985 (Box 659, Folder 17)
    - Political file, 1985 (Box 659, Folder 18)
    - Press, 1985 (Box 659, Folder 19)
    - Senate budget resolution, 1985 (Box 659, Folder 20)
    - Special interests, 1985 (Box 659, Folder 21)
    - Special mailings, 1985 (Box 659, Folder 22)
    - Special projects, 1985 (Box 660, Folder 1)
    - Staff meeting minutes, 1985 (Box 660, Folder 2)
    - Supplemental appropriations, 1985 (Box 660, Folder 3-7)
    - Susquehanna River Flood Warning Improvement Project, 1985 (Box 660, Folder 8)
    - Television tapings, 1985 (Box 660, Folder 9)
    - Tennessee Valley Authority, 1985 (Box 660, Folder 10)
    - Three Mile Island, 1985 (Box 660, Folder 11)
    - Turtle Creek Flood Control Project, 1985 (Box 660, Folder 12)
    - Water resources, 1985 (Box 660, Folder 13-14)
    - Water resources development, 1985 (Box 660, Folder 15)
    - Allegheny River Basin, 1986 (Box 660, Folder 16)
    - Budget, 1986 (Box 660, Folder 17-19)
    - Budget, 1986 (Box 661, Folder 1-2)
    - Campaign, 1986 (Box 661, Folder 3)
    - Casework reports, 1986 (Box 661, Folder 4)
    - Coal, 1986 (Box 661, Folder 5)
    - Confluence dam, 1986 (Box 661, Folder 6)
    - CMS, Abstract reports, 1986 (Box 661, Folder 7-8)
    - CMS, Mail reports, 1986 (Box 661, Folder 9-13)
    - CMS, Mass mailings, 1986 (Box 661, Folder 14)
    - CMS, Mass mailings reports, 1986 (Box 661, Folder 15)
    - CMS, Output reports, 1986 (Box 661, Folder 16)
    - CMS, Weekly item stat reports, 1986 (Box 661, Folder 17)
    - CMS, Zip and area code stats, 1986 (Box 661, Folder 18)
    - Energy and water, 1986 (Box 661, Folder 19)
    - Memos, Michel to Taylor, 1986 (Box 661, Folder 20)
    - Memos, Staff to Taylor, 1986 (Box 662, Folder 1-2)
    - Memos, Taylor to Michel, 1986 (Box 662, Folder 3)
    - Memos, Taylor to staff, 1986 (Box 662, Folder 4-5)
    - Miscellaneous, 1986 (Box 662, Folder 6-7)
    - Natural gas pricing, 1986 (Box 662, Folder 8)
    - Open houses, 1986 (Box 662, Folder 9)
    - Political file, 1986 (Box 662, Folder 10-12)
    - Pottstown flood control, 1986 (Box 662, Folder 13)
    - Press, 1986 (Box 662, Folder 14)
    - St. Christopher's Hospital, 1986 (Box 662, Folder 15)
    - Senate floor action, 1986 (Box 662, Folder 16)
    - Schedules, 1986 (Box 662, Folder 17-18)
    - Schedules, 1986 (Box 663, Folder 1-2)
    - Site visitors, 1986 (Box 663, Folder 3)
    - Susquehanna River Basin, 1986 (Box 663, Folder 4)
    - Urgent supplemental appropriations, 1986 (Box 663, Folder 5-7)
    - VIP reports, 1986 (Box 663, Folder 8)
    - Water bill, 1986 (Box 663, Folder 9)
    - Wyoming Valley flood control, 1986 (Box 663, Folder 10)
    - Appropriations, 1987 (Box 663, Folder 11)
    - Water resources, 1987 (Box 663, Folder 12-13)
  - Bill Tuerk, 1997-2006; 36.
    Bill Tuerk served as staff director, with materials dated from 1997 to 2006.
    - Authorization construction, 2006 (Box 663, Folder 14)
    - CODEL, undated (Box 663, Folder 15)
    - Cost comparison, 2005 (Box 663, Folder 16)
    - Memos, 2003-2004 (Box 663, Folder 17)
    - Veterans affairs, 1997-2003 (Box 663, Folder 18-19)
    - Veterans affairs, ACCESSeDOCS, 2005 (Box 663, Folder 20)
    - Veterans affairs, Amendments, 2005 (Box 663, Folder 21)
    - Veterans affairs, American Legion, 2005 (Box 663, Folder 22)
    - Veterans affairs, Appeals backlog, 2006 (Box 663, Folder 23)
    - Veterans affairs, Appropriations, 2005-20056 (Box 663, Folder 24)
    - Veterans affairs, John Bell, 2005 (Box 663, Folder 25)
    - Veterans affairs, Benefits backlog, 2005-2006 (Box 663, Folder 26)
    - Veterans affairs, Budget, 2005 (Box 663, Folder 27)
    - Veterans affairs, Butler County, 2003-2005 (Box 663, Folder 28)
    - Veterans affairs, Data breach, 2006 (Box 663, Folder 29)
    - Veterans affairs, DOD authorization bill, 2005 (Box 663, Folder 30)
    - Veterans affairs, Disability outreach, 2005-2006 (Box 663, Folder 31)
    - Veterans affairs, DUST, 2005 (Box 663, Folder 32)
    - Veterans affairs, Erie, 2005-2006 (Box 663, Folder 33)
    - Veterans affairs, Jon Fox, 2005 (Box 663, Folder 34)
    - Veterans affairs, Individual unemployability benefit, 2005 (Box 663, Folder 35)
    - Veterans affairs, Information technology, 2005 (Box 664, Folder 1)
    - Veterans affairs, Israel, 2005 (Box 664, Folder 2)
    - Veterans affairs, Katrina, 2005 (Box 664, Folder 3)
    - Veterans affairs, Legislation, 2005-2006 (Box 664, Folder 4)
    - Veterans affairs, Long-term care, 2005 (Box 664, Folder 5)
    - Veterans affairs, Mandatory funding, 2004-2005 (Box 664, Folder 6)
    - Veterans affairs, Medical and prosthetics research, 2006 (Box 664, Folder 7)
    - Veterans affairs, Memos, 2005 (Box 664, Folder 8)
    - Veterans affairs, Murderers at Arlington Cemetery, 2005 (Box 664, Folder 9)
    - Veterans affairs, Murray amendment, 2005 (Box 664, Folder 10)
    - Veterans affairs, Nominations, 2005-2006 (Box 664, Folder 11)
    - Veterans affairs, Organizational meeting, 2007 (Box 664, Folder 12)
    - Veterans affairs, Jonathan Perlin, 2005 (Box 664, Folder 13)
    - Veterans affairs, Pittsburgh cemetery, 2005 (Box 664, Folder 14)
    - Veterans affairs, Pride Mobility, 2005 (Box 664, Folder 15)
    - Veterans affairs, Proxy, 2005 (Box 664, Folder 16)
    - Veterans affairs, Reports, 2005 (Box 664, Folder 17)
    - Veterans affairs, Representation, 2006 (Box 664, Folder 18)
    - Veterans affairs, Shortfall, 2005 (Box 664, Folder 19)
    - Veterans affairs, Randall Shughart, 2005 (Box 664, Folder 20)
    - Veterans affairs, Stolen Valor Act, 2006 (Box 664, Folder 21)
    - Veterans affairs, James Terry, 2005 (Box 664, Folder 22)
    - Veterans affairs, Testimony, 2005 (Box 664, Folder 23)
    - Veterans affairs, Tri-State Veterans, 2006 (Box 664, Folder 24)
  - David Urban, 1997-2001; 37.
    David Urban served as chief of staff, 1998-2002.
    - Chronological file, December 1997 (Box 664, Folder 25)
    - Correspondence, 1997 (Box 664, Folder 26)
    - Faxes, 1997 (Box 664, Folder 27)
    - Letters of recommendation, 2001 (Box 664, Folder 28)
    - Miscellaneous, 1999 (Box 664, Folder 29)
  - Andrew Wallace, 1984-2010; 38.
    Andrew Wallace served as executive director, Allentown/Scranton/Wilkes-Barre offices, 1984-2010.
    - Local issues, Barnes Kasson Jospital, Lackawanna County Treatment Court, Sallie Mae, 2006-2009 (Box 664, Folder 30)
    - Local issues, Dairy, Pride Mobility, Wall Street West, 2005-2008 (Box 664, Folder 31)
    - Local issues, Environment, 2005-2009 (Box 664, Folder 32-33)
    - Local issues, Medical college meeting, 2006-2010 (Box 664, Folder 34-35)
    - Local issues, Military, Scranton and Tobyhanna, 2007-2009 (Box 664, Folder 36)
    - Local issues, Wilkes-Barre, 2006-2009 (Box 664, Folder 37)
    - Local issues, Transportation, Focus 81 Committee, 2006-2010 (Box 664, Folder 38)
    - Local issues, Transportation, Hazleton/Scranton Intermodal Transit Centers, Wilkes-Barre/Scranton International Airport, 2007-2009 (Box 664, Folder 39)
    - Local issues, Transportation, New York rail service, 1999-2009 (Box 665, Folder 1-2)
    - Local issues, Wage index, 2006-2008 (Box 665, Folder 3)
    - Marjol, 1998-2000 (Box 665, Folder 4)
    - Marjol, 2001 (Box 665, Folder 5-6)
    - Marjol, 2002-2009 (Box 665, Folder 7)
    - Marjol, EPA meeting, October 1999 (Box 665, Folder 8)
    - Marjol, EPA meeting, January-August 2000 (Box 665, Folder 9)
    - Marjol, EPA meeting, December 2000 (Box 665, Folder 10)
    - Marjol, EPA meeting, February-May 2001 (Box 665, Folder 11)
    - Marjol, Newsclips, 1990-2001 (Box 665, Folder 12)
    - Marjol, OIG meeting, October 2002 (Box 665, Folder 13)
    - Marjol, Ombudsman, 2000-2001 (Box 665, Folder 14-15)
    - Marjol, Ombudsman, Hugh Kaufman, 2001-2002 (Box 665, Folder 16-17)
    - Precision National Plating, 1997-2000 (Box 666, Folder 1)
    - Precision National Plating, 2000-2001 (Box 666, Folder 2)
    - Precision National Plating, 2001-2002 (Box 666, Folder 3-4)
    - Precision National Plating, Meetings, 1999-2000 (Box 666, Folder 5)
    - Precision National Plating, Meetings, 2000 (Box 666, Folder 6-7)
    - Precision National Plating, Meetings, 2007 (Box 666, Folder 8)
    - Tranguch, 2001 (Box 666, Folder 9-12)
    - Tranguch, 2001-2002 (Box 666, Folder 13)
    - Tranguch, Briefings, 2002 (Box 666, Folder 14)
    - Tranguch, Meetings with administration, 2002 (Box 667, Folder 1)
    - Tranguch, Meetings with administration, 2002-2003 (Box 667, Folder 2)
    - Trip files, January-May 1984 (Box 667, Folder 3)
    - Trip files, June-December 1984 (Box 667, Folder 4)
    - Trip files, January-May 1985 (Box 667, Folder 5)
    - Trip files, June-September 1985 (Box 667, Folder 6)
    - Trip files, October 1985-April 1986 (Box 667, Folder 7)
    - Trip files, May 1986-January 1987 (Box 667, Folder 8)
    - Trip files, May-December 1987 (Box 667, Folder 9)
    - Trip files, February 1988-September 1989 (Box 667, Folder 10)
    - Trip files, January-February 1990 (Box 667, Folder 11)
    - Trip files, April-June 1990 (Box 667, Folder 12)
    - Trip files, July 1990-March 1991 (Box 667, Folder 13)
    - Trip files, April-June 1991 (Box 667, Folder 14)
    - Trip files, July-December 1991 (Box 668, Folder 1)
    - Trip files, January-July 1992 (Box 668, Folder 2)
    - Trip files, August-December 1992 (Box 668, Folder 3)
    - Trip files, February 1993-February 1995 (Box 668, Folder 4)
    - Trip files, April 1995-April 1996 (Box 668, Folder 5)
    - Trip files, May-December 1996 (Box 668, Folder 6)
    - Trip files, February-September 1997 (Box 668, Folder 7)
    - Trip files, October 1997-May 1998 (Box 668, Folder 8)
    - Trip files, August 1998-July 1999 (Box 668, Folder 9)
    - Trip files, December 1999-December 2000 (Box 668, Folder 10)
    - Trip files, February-June 2001 (Box 668, Folder 11)
    - Trip files, July 2001-April 2002 (Box 668, Folder 12)
    - Trip files, May-December 2002 (Box 668, Folder 13)
    - Trip files, March-August 2003 (Box 669, Folder 1)
    - Trip files, September-November 2003 (Box 669, Folder 2)
    - Trip files, February-March 2004 (Box 669, Folder 3)
    - Trip files, April 2004-November 2005 (Box 669, Folder 4)
    - Trip files, May 2006-April 2007 (Box 669, Folder 5)
    - Trip files, May-November 2007 (Box 669, Folder 6)
    - Trip files, January-September 2008 (Box 669, Folder 7)
    - Trip files, October 2008 (Box 669, Folder 8)
    - Trip files, December 2008-February 2009 (Box 669, Folder 9)
    - Trip files, March-December 2009 (Box 669, Folder 10)
    - Trip files, January-May 2010 (Box 669, Folder 11)
  - Bill Wilcox, 1981-1982; 39.
    Bill Wilcox served as staff assistant, 1981-1982.
    - Chronological files, February 1981 (Box 669, Folder 12)
    - Chronological files, March 1981 (Box 669, Folder 13-14)
    - Chronological files, April 1981 (Box 669, Folder 15)
    - Chronological files, April 1981 (Box 670, Folder 1)
    - Chronological files, May 1981 (Box 670, Folder 2-3)
    - Chronological files, June 1981 (Box 670, Folder 4-5)
    - Chronological files, July 1981 (Box 670, Folder 6-7)
    - Chronological files, August 1981 (Box 670, Folder 8)
    - Chronological files, September 1981 (Box 670, Folder 9-10)
    - Chronological files, October 1981 (Box 670, Folder 11-12)
    - Chronological files, November 1981 (Box 670, Folder 13-15)
    - Chronological files, December 1981 (Box 671, Folder 1-2)
    - Chronological files, January 1982 (Box 671, Folder 3-4)
    - Chronological files, February 1982 (Box 671, Folder 5-6)
    - Chronological files, March 1982 (Box 671, Folder 7-10)
    - Constituent services, 1981-1982 (Box 671, Folder 11)
    - Constitution, 1981-1982 (Box 671, Folder 12-13)
    - Construction, 1981 (Box 671, Folder 14)
    - Copyrighted television programs, 1981-1982 (Box 671, Folder 15)
    - Defense, 1982 (Box 671, Folder 16)
    - Diagnostic center, Philadelphia, 1982 (Box 671, Folder 17)
    - Industrial Development Bank, 1981-1982 (Box 671, Folder 18)
    - Letters, Budget, 1982 (Box 671, Folder 19)
    - Memos to administrators, 1981 (Box 672, Folder 1)
    - Memos to Specter, 1981 (Box 672, Folder 2-3)
    - Memos to Specter, 1982 (Box 672, Folder 4)
    - S. 1720, 1981-1982 (Box 672, Folder 5-8)
    - S. 1720, Bill text, 1981 (Box 672, Folder 9)
    - S. 1720, Incoming letters, 1981-1982 (Box 672, Folder 10)
  - Gordon Woodrow, Jr., 1980-1983; 40.
    Gordon Woodrow, Jr. served as: chief of staff, 1981-1984; and administrative assistant, Philadelphia office, 1985-1990.
    - American List Counsel, undated (Box 672, Folder 11)
    - Briefing book, 1981 (Box 672, Folder 12)
    - Builder, 1982 (Box 672, Folder 13)
    - The CEO and Washington, 1981 (Box 672, Folder 14)
    - Committee on Congressional Redistricting statement, 1981 (Box 672, Folder 15)
    - Compilation of reports and statements, 1982 (Box 672, Folder 16)
    - Constituent mail, 1981-1982 (Box 672, Folder 17)
    - Directory of organizations, 1982 (Box 672, Folder 18)
    - Doing Business with the Federal Government, 1982 (Box 672, Folder 19)
    - Final budget, 1980-1981 (Box 673, Folder 1)
    - General, 1981-1982 (Box 673, Folder 2)
    - Letters, 1982 (Box 673, Folder 3)
    - Letters of recommendation and requests, 1981-1982 (Box 673, Folder 4)
    - National Republican Senatorial Committee backgrounder, 1982 (Box 673, Folder 5)
    - National Steel Corporation, 1982 (Box 673, Folder 6)
    - Newsclips, 1981-1982 (Box 673, Folder 7)
    - Office reports, 1982 (Box 673, Folder 8)
    - Staff travel reports, 1981 (Box 673, Folder 9)
    - Staff travel reports, 1982 (Box 673, Folder 10)
    - Staff travel reports, 1983 (Box 673, Folder 11)
    - Trip files, Pittsburgh, October 1982 (Box 673, Folder 12)
    - Trip files, Voyage House, December 1982 (Box 673, Folder 13)
    - Trip files, Harrisburg, 1983 (Box 673, Folder 14)
    - Voting record analysis, 1981 (Box 673, Folder 15)
- Memos, 1981-2010; II.
  Memos contains intra-office memos amongst the staff and Senator Specter. Topics covered include schedules, information on legislative and trip preparation, and various other topics. The series is arranged chronologically.
  - February 1981-March 1984 (Box 674)
  - April 1984-December 1996 (Box 675)
  - January 1997-December 2002 (Box 676)
  - January 2003-September 2004 (Box 677)
  - October 2004-October 2005 (Box 678)
  - November 2005-May 2006 (Box 679)
  - June 2006-March 2007 (Box 680)
  - April 2007-April 2008 (Box 681)
  - May 2008-February 2009 (Box 682)
  - March 2009-December 2009 (Box 683)
  - January-October 2010 (Box 684)
- Office Management, 1981-2001; III.
  Office Management contains records related to the daily management of Senator Specter's office. This includes information on tours, policies, and guidelines. The series is arranged alphabetically by subject.
  - CIA recommendations, 1993-1995 (Box 685, Folder 1)
  - Congressional Accountability Act, 1995-1996 (Box 685, Folder 2)
  - Congressional interns and volunteers orientation materials, 2001 (Box 685, Folder 3)
  - Federal Protective Service brochures, undated (Box 685, Folder 4)
  - Floor privileges, 1981-1984 (Box 685, Folder 5)
  - Forms, 1980s (Box 685, Folder 6)
  - Franked mail rules, 1996 (Box 685, Folder 7)